## ADENIGBA AHMED ADEFOLARIN

No 4 olarenwaju Oloruntele street, opposite mobil, mile 12, Lagos State +2349011464174
Lameda789@gmail.com

A junior developer with a year experience building responsive and interactive web sites, core strength writing HTML5 and CSS3 while been fluent in JavaScript and ReactJs. The aforementioned skills have been put to use while working on both solo as well as collaborative projects some of which are already hosted online.

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Date of Birth: 12/12/1997 State of Origin: KWARA

L.G.A: IFELODUN
Nationality: NIGERIA
Marital Status: SINGLE

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Usmanu Danfodiyo University
Bachelor's Degree (MICROBIOLOGY)

**Sokoto, Sokoto State** November 2014 - September 2018

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

TIIDELAB Abuja

**Prefellowship Cohort** 

March 2022 – April 2022

Using only HTML and CSS, I was able to construct and launch both my personal web portfolio and a contact page for an e-commerce website within the duration of the program. During the program, I was also able to hone my skills in using Git and GitHub because my team and I were given a group project where the requirement for cooperation necessitated the usage of these tools.

TIIDELAB Abuja

Cohort 4 Fellowship JUNE 2022 – presently

The two skill I'm honing as a fellow in TIIDELab are ReactJs and JavaScript. Additionally, I'm honing my soft skills, which will enable me to develop into a developer who is unique in both technical and intellectual terms.

# TE

TECHNICAL SKILLS	
•	Familiar with python programming language.
•	HTML5 and CSS3
•	JavaScript
•	Bootstrap
•	ReactJs
•	Git and GitHub
•	Microsoft Office Packages
SOFT SKILLS	
	Critical and Analytical thinking
	Attention to details
	Leadership skills
	Team work
	Digital skills
	Creative
•	Good communication skills
PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT AND CERTIFICATION	
	Certificate of completion (TIIDELab Cohort 4 Prefellowship Program (Fundamentals of Software Development))
REFERENCE	
Available upon request.	